{
  "openingRemarks": "each factor between 6 and 9",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(7 \\times 9\\)",
      "answer": "63"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 \\times 7\\)",
      "answer": "42"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 \\times 8\\)",
      "answer": "64"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 \\times 7\\)",
      "answer": "56"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 \\times 9\\)",
      "answer": "54"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 \\times 9\\)",
      "answer": "72"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 \\times 6\\)",
      "answer": "48"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 \\times 6\\)",
      "answer": "42"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 \\times 8\\)",
      "answer": "72"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 \\times 7\\)",
      "answer": "63"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 \\times 8\\)",
      "answer": "48"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 \\times 9\\)",
      "answer": "81"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 \\times 7\\)",
      "answer": "49"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 \\times 8\\)",
      "answer": "56"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 \\times 6\\)",
      "answer": "36"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9 \\times 6\\)",
      "answer": "54"
    }
  ]
}
